

PROFILE

Hello,i'm 18 yers old web developer from Uzbekistan from Tashkent. I learned MERN,I have experienced in the field of frontend as a website developer. I have been coding for couples of years in series of jobs



tigeruzb777@gmail.com

93 106-38-13



Uzbekistan, Tashkent



All my works are here

https://muffix.netlify.app/

MO'MINOV XIKMATILLA

WEB DEVELOPER



EXPERIENCES

Jan, 2021 - Present

FREELANCER AND ONLINE/OFFLINE TEACHER

- I'm teaching about web development,i like teaching and i have a lot of students
- i work at Ibrat talim learning centre and Lavina-tech
- I'm a freelancer also

Aug, 2020 - Oct, 2020

FulFil education

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

 I worked at FulFil education about 3 months as a Frontend developer



EDUCATIONS

Dec, 2019 - Aug, 2021

MUIMI - SPECIALIZED BOARDING SCHOOL

Sep, 2021 - Jan, 2021

LEAP ENGLISH EDUCATION CENTRE REGISTON LEARNING CENTRE

2019 - 2021

BASICS OF PROGRAMMING AND ALGORITHMS BY SENIOR DEVELOPER DONIYOR TAGOEV THEN ONLINE LEARNING BY YOUTUBE

Oct, 2021 - Present

MERN COURSE



SKILLS

- Html 5
- Css3
- vanilla Js, es6,es7 ...
- Sass
- Animate css/js
- React
- Redux (in progress)
- English

- Communication Skill
- mentor ability
- Creative
- ability to work in a team